owb.com 2018-10-29

# Privacy & Security | OneWest Bank

## Last Updated: March 2018

  * Introduction
  * Personal information we collect
  * How we use the personal information we collect
  * How we may share personal information you provide to us
  * How we protect the confidentiality and security of your Personal Information
  * Children
  * Information we automatically collect (not Personal Information)
  * Do-Not-Track Signals
  * Changes to this Policy, and contact information

### Introduction

CIT Group Inc. and its affiliates (collectively "CIT," "we," "us," or "our") respect your privacy and are committed to treating and using Personal Information (as defined below) about you responsibly.

This Online Privacy Policy ("Policy") explains CIT's online practices to collect, use and share Personal Information from or about you except as otherwise provided in this Policy. This Policy applies both to any CIT site and/or mobile application that links to this Policy (such sites and/or mobile applications, and all activities thereon, constituting "the Services"). This Policy applies regardless of what computer or device ("computer") you use to access the Services.

Throughout this Policy, we refer to nonpublic personal information that can directly and without additional information identify you or your accounts as "Personal Information." "Personal Information" includes information such as your name, address, email address, or phone number and other information that is not otherwise publicly available (such as your date of birth, Social Security number and financial information). Please read this Policy carefully. When you visit this site you consent to the terms of this Policy and the information described herein.

Any dispute related to this Policy will be governed by our Terms of Use.

If you have a financial product or service with us, we will use and share any information that we collect from or about you in accordance with our Consumer Privacy Notice.

Back to top

### Personal information we collect

We collect Personal Information from and about you in order to identify you as our customer, establish and manage customer accounts (including collection activity), complete customer transactions and understand our customers and their needs. We also collect this information to improve how we market products and services, learn about our markets and design and improve our products and services. Furthermore the collection of this information helps us to comply with legal and regulatory requirements, and protect the rights, property, or safety of CIT, its employees, customers, visitors to the Services, and others.

We may also collect Personal Information from you if you

  1. apply for employment through the Services (which may include your name, address, references and employment history)
  2. use the Services to check the status of your accounts (such as your name, account number and login password); and
  3. send us an email to inquire about your account or to request information (such as your name, email address and any other Personal Information you supply in your message).

Back to top

### How we use the Personal Information we collect

We may use the Personal Information that you provide to us as follows:

  1. if you apply for a job, to consider you for the position and to contact references (please note that your references may be contacted without prior notice to you); or
  2. if you apply for credit, to assess your creditworthiness including retrieving credit reports and to approve or reject your application; or
  3. to respond to inquiries you may have about your account and other related matters; or
  4. if you send us an email for information, to reply to your request.

Back to top

### How we may share Personal Information you provide to us

Please see the CIT Consumer Privacy Notice for information on how Personal Information may be shared.

Unless our Consumer Privacy Notice provides otherwise CIT may share your Personal Information under the following circumstances:

Affiliates: We may share your name, address and information about your transactions and experiences with us (such as your payment history or other facts about your account) with our affiliates.

Agents and service providers: To establish, administer, and manage our customers' accounts, evaluate credit, provide customer service and benefits, process account transactions and account statements, engage in collections activities, or process job applications, we may disclose your Personal Information to companies that work with us to perform services or business operations on our behalf. We may also share your Personal Information with companies that perform marketing services on our behalf, or with other financial institutions (including insurance companies) with whom we have joint marketing agreements.

Nonaffiliated third parties: In certain instances, we are permitted or even required to disclose your Personal Information to nonaffiliated third parties. For example, reporting your transaction history and information with us to credit reporting agencies, responding to regulators or auditors, to protect against fraud, or to provide information in connection with proposed or actual business transactions involving CIT companies or accounts. We may also disclose your Personal Information to third parties when legally compelled to do so, such as to comply with the law, to enforce our terms of use, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of CIT, its employees, customers, visitors to these Services, and others. Please be aware that these disclosures are permitted by law without your consent.

Other third parties: We may also share, as permitted by law, or unless our Consumer Privacy Notice provides otherwise, your Personal Information with other third parties with whom we do not have joint marketing agreements, such as other financial services providers, insurance companies, or with nonfinancial companies such as service organizations, retailers, travel services and direct marketers. We require these companies to adhere to CIT's confidentiality standards with respect to your Personal Information.

USA Patriot Act Section 326 compliance: When you open an account with us, we will ask for your name, address, and other identifying documents such as your driver's license, that will allow us to identify you. We do this to help the government fight the funding of terrorism and money laundering activities. U.S. federal law requires all financial institutions to obtain, verify and record information that identifies each person who opens an account.

Business transfers: As we develop our business, we may sell or buy businesses or assets, or be involved in mergers or other corporate reorganization. In transactions such as these, your Personal Information may be shared in connection with any of the foregoing types of transactions, even prior to the existence of a final, binding, agreement to buy, sell, merge, or reorganize.

Back to top

### How we protect the confidentiality and security of your Personal Information

CIT uses reasonable measures to protect Personal Information from unauthorized access, deletion or alteration. In addition, we have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your Personal Information. As part of our security practices, CIT does not send requests for Personal Information to our customers. Any Personal Information you request CIT to send you via email, such as your account balance, is encrypted. However, standard email communications are not. Therefore, you should not transmit your Personal Information to us through email. Please note that no company can guarantee perfect online security, and please remain careful and vigilant in your online activities.

Back to top

### Children

CIT operates general audience online Services that are accessible to the public. These Services are not intended for visitors under 18 years of age. We do not knowingly market our products or services to children, nor do we knowingly collect Personal Information from children.

Back to top

### Information we automatically collect (not Personal Information)

When you visit or browse our Services, we may collect information such as your Internet Protocol or "IP" address, the "URL" of the web pages you visit, and we may use "cookies," web beacons, or other objects to collect statistical and other information about your use of our Services. The purpose of collecting this information is to improve the effectiveness of our Services and product offerings. The collected information may include, for example, information about your computer, its unique identifiers, and its configuration, the web pages you visited or mobile applications used; the date and time of your visit; the websites you visited immediately before and after visiting our web site; your language preference; demographic and/or location-based information; and the popularity of various advertising words and phrases used by us. The collection of this information allows for the compilation of aggregate and anonymous information about the usage of our Services, and can help us improve your use of our Services, for example, providing quick login, streamlining site navigation and maintaining up-to-date content for all users. Should you configure your browser to reject cookies, you may disable some of our Service's features.

Back to top

### Online Behavioral Advertising, "Cookies", and Similar Technologies

CIT and our digital partners (e.g. ad network or agency) may use cookies, mobile advertising identifiers, and other information for the purposes of delivering tailored advertising to you on third-party websites.

Cookies are pieces of data stored by your browser. They are used by web servers to uniquely distinguish your browser from all others and remember your browser over time, including preferences and other information. Cookies are associated with particular web domains and are transmitted to a web server when your browser opens a page or sends a network request to that domain. We and our partners may also use web beacons with or without cookies for various purposes, including analytics and targeting interest-based advertising. Web beacons are small image files that are loaded when a web page or other online resource is processed by your browser (including when emails are opened). For mobile applications, advertising identifiers set by the device are used, together with other information, to generate usage analytics and target ads.

If you click on one of our ads on a third-party website, cookies may also be used to track the effectiveness of our online advertising and for the purposes of delivering ads that may be relevant to you in the future.

You can opt-out of having our partners use your web browsing behavior for purposes of serving interest-based advertising by opting out [here](http://optout.aboutads.info/ "Opt-out of having our partners use your web browsing behavior").

Please note this opt-out works via cookies, so if you delete cookies, use a different device, or change web browsers, you will need to opt-out again.

You may still see some of our untailored ads, but these will not be served to you based on your inferred interests or web browsing activity on our CIT websites.

Back to top

### Do-Not-Track-Signals

We currently do not employ technology that changes how our servers treat your browser if our servers receive a "do-not-track" signal from your browser. 

Back to top

### Changes to this Policy, and contact information

CIT may update this Policy from time to time. CIT may notify you of an update to this Policy by any reasonable means, including by email, online account notification, mobile application pop-up, or regular mail. You agree that if you choose to continue to use the Services after CIT sends you such an e-mail, online account notification, mobile application pop-up, or regular mail (allowing one week from the sent date for delivery of regular mail), you are bound to the most recent version of the Policy. You should periodically check the effective date at the top of this Policy to be sure that you are aware of the most recent version of this Policy and the important information described in it.

Back to top
